<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ExpandableRecyclerview</string>

    <string name="new_1">Mr Bidens new goal includes having 160 million adults fully vaccinated by Independence Day.
The target is well within reach as 105 million have already had the required jabs, and the US is vaccinating nearly a million adults per day.
But the vaccination rate is half of what it was just three weeks ago.</string>
    <string name="new_2">The government last week extended the gap between two doses of the Covishield Covid-19 vaccine to 12-16 weeks,
up from the previous maximum of eight weeks, on the recommendation of the National Technical Advisory Group on Immunisation (NTAGI).</string>
    <string name="new_3">West Bengal chief minister Mamata Banerjee has announced that local train services shall be suspended in the state from Thursday onwards
to combat the worsening coronavirus disease (Covid-19) pandemic situation. Meanwhile, metro rail and government-run transport services in
West Bengal shall operate with 50% occupancy from Thursday, the chief minister announced.</string>
    <string name="new_4">In his letter to the states/UTs, Union home secretary Ajay Kumar Bhalla said that in the context of recent fire incidents and the impending
summer season, either because of high temperature, lack of maintenance or high load on the internal wirings within the facilities, short circuiting takes place,
leading to fire incidents and consequential loss of life and essential infrastructure.</string>
    <string name="new_5">Gary Newman, 73, who has been stranded in India since March last year, filed a lawsuit against the Scott Morrison government also for threatening to prosecute
those attempting to enter Australia with the possibility of a jail term and a penalty.</string>
    <string name="new_6">Kaushiks wife was also getting treatment at the same hospital after contracting the virus but she is recovering well and is likely to be discharged this week.
My mother has recovered now and she should be discharged within 2-3 days Ehsan said.
Kaushik had coached both the senior mens and womens teams. Under his coaching, India mens team had won its last major international tournament, the 1998 Asian Games</string>
    <string name="new_7">The hospitals in Delhi have been reporting shortage of oxygen supplies, beds and essential medicines as the health infrastructure continues to crumble under the pressure of the
unprecedented rise in the number of Covid-19 patients requiring oxygen or ICU support.</string>
    <string name="new_8">In a perfect example of communal harmony, a church in Barcelona opened its doors for Muslims breaking fast during the holy month of Ramadan. As indoor venues remain closed in
the country, the Catholic church offered its open-air cloisters for people to eat and pray together.</string>
    <string name="new_9">The bugs only emerge in large numbers when the ground temperature reaches 64 degrees. … Cicadas evolved a key survival technique: overwhelming numbers. Theres just too many
of them to all get eaten when they all emerge at once, so some will survive and reproduce, Raupp says. This is not an invasion</string>
    <string name="new_10">The 56-year-old woman rights activist was made the chairperson of the special task force on rape, trafficking and violence against women, constituted by the Centre in 2012 after
the Nirbhaya case in Delhi. She was also the brain behind the Nirbhoy Gram, a campaign in Malda district of West Bengal focusing on empowering villages for safety and security of women and children.</string>


</resources>